# W.C. "Connor" Scofield

Driven professional, and a team player with proven leadership capabilities. I have worked in a variety of fields including NBA account sales, food and customer service, and large event marketing, logistics and management. I am a Georgia Tech certified developer, with a strong ability to grasp new technologies and languages.. I have practiced time management and learned how to succeed under pressure throughout my work experiences, collegiate studies and extracurricular activities.

270 Robin Hood Road Atlanta, Ga, 30309 (404) 783-1463 wcc.scofield@gmail.com

### **EXPERIENCE**

# The Atlanta Hawks, Atlanta, Ga— Membership Consultant

July, 2017 - December, 2017

Acted as a personal consultant of Philips Arena responsible for the recruitment of new season and group ticket memberships, servicing incoming requests and issues from ticket holders, and providing additional support to the ticket and market departments when necessary.

# Emory Law Clinic for Veterans, Atlanta, Ga— Intern

May, 2017 - July, 2017

Acted as an assistant to the Emory Law Clinic's attorney, partaking in tasks such as discovery of evidence, brief editing, exhibit organization, and client interviewing

# **Striking Market**, Atlanta, Ga — Event Zone Lead

January, 2016

Managed pre-event load-in for the "2016 Smite World Gaming Championship" at the Cobb Energy Center.

Acted as a "Zone Lead", responsible for overseeing customer service, management of shift rotations, personnel placement, talent services and client accommodation.

### **EDUCATION**

# **Elon University**, Elon, NC— B.A. in Political Science

August, 2013 - May, 2017

# **Georgia Institute of Technology,** Atlanta, Ga— Full Stack Web Development Certificate

March, 2018 - May, 2018

#### **Front-End Skills**

Proficient with Javascript, jQuery, AJAX, HTML/CSS, Bootstrap and Materialize. Working knowledge of React

### **Back-End Skills**

Proficient with Node/Express, MySQL, MongoDB and Mongoose, JWT

## **Project Management**

Acted as project lead for "Concert Connection" a ticket and concert finder application.

Acted as project lead for "Cella" industrial commercial real estate manager and provider application.

## **Programs**

UGA Interdisciplinary Field Program — Student May, 2015 - July, 2016

Elon in D.C. Experience— Fellow January, 2017

Elon Club Ultimate — Captain and Leadership Council August, 2013 - May, 2017

### **LANGUAGES**

English, Spanish